sup everyone came is only five for the
very special video today and today I
would like you to discuss with you guys
about something that I know you want to
discuss with me and it's about shotgun
hasn't been getting like a love hate
videos recently look I don't know
exactly no wife if I what you have what
do you guess it's because of that new
stupid SOG nerds like movie just came
out so people who don't know anything
that saw their talk or song I'm gonna in
general they are literally just really
funny about Sonic on the ground and they
are making video saying all oh it's bad
oh it's got bad music the animation is
[ __ ] and I gotta tell all of you people
who making those videos just stop I mean
why are you trying to be funny nobody
thinks you're being funny as a matter
fact the reason I'm making this video is
because there was a fan of my new
channel
he sent me messages sending to another
video where it's some guy making
thumb-sucking around because it's cool
to do it right now I guess I mean it's
cool some [ __ ] to a talking around I
mean I'm not surprised mo mo most people
don't even know anything about Sonic
Arun so obviously here here let me give
you example [ __ ] when I went to that
video and [ __ ] on the video he literally
said the origin trip three episodes at
the Stalag beginning how me or something
you know that [ __ ] that he said all of
the episode order was wrong he he said
the episodes war episodes 36 no 26 28
and 30 26 28 and 30 and he said why is
absolu the beginnings episode 28 and
then he started laughing like he's was
like laughing and [ __ ] and all I could
think was [ __ ] [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
that is the TV order he was trying to
say suck on the ground was bad because
the episode beginnings which every true
Sonic enough and knows is episode number
one and you're probably if you're stupid
you're quite thinking like him why was
it episode 28 well I'll tell you why
[ __ ] because that was the TV order you
see when you go to wiki or Wikipedia if
you are in the episode list is in TV
order so in other words if people are
watching that that order they're gonna
get it wrong it's not the accurate canon
order idiots it [ __ ] piss look at
this [ __ ] [ __ ] if I look at the DVD
and I get the [ __ ] order there it is
on that's why I'm - if I get disc one
and look at the back there is beginnings
origins poets power one two and three
I mean I do I gotta it's just it's so
[ __ ] annoying because when I watch
sock Underground I love that [ __ ] I get
bullied every day of my [ __ ] life and
you think that's funny [ __ ] you people
think that's funny like haha that's
laugh at the only taco fan in the whole
[ __ ] wall and [ __ ] because he likes
something better than us well yeah you
know what is better you [ __ ] [ __ ]
I mean why do I gotta say all this
I mean it's [ __ ] stupid I mean I mean
here here's the deal I don't mind if
people bully me I mean it happens every
day I'm used to having my whole child
was it when I grew up it's still going
on now
like if I go down and scroll down I
guarantee this video already has a
dislike I can guarantee that [ __ ]
[ __ ] and here's what bothers me I mean
this is let's just talk you and me this
is what really likewise mass with it's
not when I get bullied it's when it's
when my my fan my fans or oh well I like
to call them my friends when I see them
getting bullied that's what really hurts
me and dammit it [ __ ] pisses me off
because I know as I was saying I hate
seeing people get made fun of for
something that they love I have to go
through all every day off and I it hurts
me because I know they'll people unlike
me they can't take it and [ __ ] like me
like people will trash talk my videos
I'll say ok I mean you make a 30 minute
animation and tell me and show it to me
when you get done oh you don't want to
because you're not good enough ok then
bye [ __ ] I'll [ __ ] you in the ass
that's that's usually how it goes and
then they I mean that's basically the
lock routine people touch on me I tell
them you make a video of them [ __ ] show
me that I'm wrong
do it [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] come on I'm
waiting I'm waiting and then they just
don't be never apply